{"experimentVersion":"mapping_practice","participantID":"t","participantAge":"t","participantGender":1,"confirmationCode":"0861271","participantFeedback":"","transferCounterbalance":false,"intermingledTrials":false,"totalTrials":16,"dataRecordFrequency":0.03999999910593033,"restbreakDuration":30.0,"getReadyDuration":3.0,"totalExperimentTime":0.0,"trialList":[0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15],"scannerTriggerTimes":[],"allTrialData":[{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[0],"mapName":"Persistent","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"controlStateOrder":[],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[0.0],"totalMovementTime":[0.0],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":0.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false],"FLAG_frameRateError":[false],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":1,"trialListIndex":[1],"mapName":"InformationScreen","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"controlStateOrder":[],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[0.0],"totalMovementTime":[0.0],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":0.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false],"FLAG_frameRateError":[false],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":2,"trialListIndex":[2],"mapName":"BeforeStartingScreen","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"controlStateOrder":[],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[0.0],"totalMovementTime":[0.0],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":0.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false],"FLAG_frameRateError":[false],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":3,"trialListIndex":[3],"mapName":"ConsentScreen","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"controlStateOrder":[],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[0.0],"totalMovementTime":[0.0],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":0.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false],"FLAG_frameRateError":[false],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":4,"trialListIndex":[4],"mapName":"StartScreen","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"controlStateOrder":[],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[0.0],"totalMovementTime":[0.0],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":0.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false],"FLAG_frameRateError":[false],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":5,"trialListIndex":[5],"mapName":"InstructionsScreen","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"controlStateOrder":[],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[0.0],"totalMovementTime":[0.0],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":0.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false],"FLAG_frameRateError":[false],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Practice","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0}],"controlStateOrder":["Human","Computer"],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":60.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[1.506844162940979,1.2128267288208008,1.507596492767334,1.654414176940918],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[1.582769751548767,2.4645156860351564,2.0895328521728517,1.7854597568511963],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":2.39863920211792,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Practice","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0}],"controlStateOrder":["Human","Computer"],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":60.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[1.3186196088790894,1.2076292037963868,1.4617135524749756,1.6953624486923218],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[2.660661220550537,3.2359774112701418,3.792665958404541,3.8159639835357668],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":2.545304298400879,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Practice","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0}],"controlStateOrder":["Human","Computer"],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":60.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[3.4294772148132326,0.7276260852813721,2.1254770755767824,1.899863839149475],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[2.0161380767822267,3.1483755111694338,3.1125924587249758,1.7457983493804932],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":2.0078787803649904,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Practice","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0}],"controlStateOrder":["Human","Computer"],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":60.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[1.2243354320526124,1.2714760303497315,0.9734897613525391,3.102091073989868],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[3.356523036956787,2.371870994567871,3.1855239868164064,4.945390701293945],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":2.145120620727539,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Practice","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0}],"controlStateOrder":["Human","Computer"],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":60.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[1.355635166168213,1.050933599472046,4.112974166870117,1.9425485134124756],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[3.236264944076538,2.278347969055176,2.568105697631836,3.6395535469055177],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":3.788088321685791,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Practice","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0}],"controlStateOrder":["Human","Computer"],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":60.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[0.8879069089889526,0.5743777751922607,1.2760804891586304,1.6566407680511475],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[2.5952396392822267,1.6743218898773194,2.227025032043457,1.8925747871398926],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":2.2058489322662355,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Practice","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0}],"controlStateOrder":["Human","Computer"],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":60.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[2.295766830444336,0.8450618982315064,1.1927921772003174,0.6856122016906738],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[3.586336374282837,3.1909189224243166,2.6777992248535158,2.0184316635131838],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":2.7363247871398927,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Practice","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0}],"controlStateOrder":["Human","Computer"],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":60.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[1.863778829574585,1.2745330333709717,2.0373141765594484,0.6305859088897705],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[1.6614034175872803,2.0916688442230226,5.116431713104248,1.5806745290756226],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":3.8232691287994386,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"GetReady","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"controlStateOrder":[],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":0.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Exit","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"controlStateOrder":[],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":0.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]}]}